<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lunch on The Om Nommy</title>
    <link>/lunch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in lunch on The Om Nommy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/lunch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Banh Mi</title>
      <link>/lunch/lunch3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lunch/lunch3/</guid>
      <description>Banh Mi This banh mi (Vietnamese sandwich) is made with chicken and full of pickled vegetables.
Prep: 30 mins
Cook: 20 mins
Total: 50 mins
Servings:2 2
Yield: 1 12-inch sandwich
Ingredients ½ cup rice vinegar ¼ cup white sugar ¼ cup water ¼ cup matchstick-cut carrots ¼ cup peeled and matchstick-cut daikon radish ¼ cup thinly sliced white onion 1 skinless, boneless chicken breast half 1 pinch garlic salt, or to taste ground black pepper to taste 1 (12 inch) French baguette 4 tablespoons mayonnaise ¼ cup thinly sliced cucumber 1 tablespoon fresh cilantro leaves 1 small jalapeno pepper, cut into 1/16-inch-thick matchsticks 1 wedge lime Directions Step 1 Combine rice vinegar, sugar, and water in a saucepan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grilled Chicken Salad Sandwich</title>
      <link>/lunch/lunch2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lunch/lunch2/</guid>
      <description>Grilled Chicken Salad Sandwich This is a great way to use leftover grilled chicken breasts from dinner the night before.
Prep: 15 mins
Total: 15 mins
Servings: 4
Yield: 4 sandwiches
Ingredients 1 cup mayonnaise ⅛ teaspoon ground black pepper ⅛ teaspoon garlic powder ⅛ teaspoon celery salt 4 cups chopped leftover grilled chicken 2 celery stalks, sliced ½ cup sweetened dried cranberries ⅔ cup salted cashews 8 slices bread, toasted 4 tablespoons mayonnaise 4 large red leaf lettuce leaves 1 ripe tomato, sliced Directions Step 1 Whisk together 1 cup of mayonnaise, pepper, garlic powder, and celery salt until combined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lunch: Spicy Grilled Cheese Sandwich</title>
      <link>/lunch/lunch1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lunch/lunch1/</guid>
      <description>Spicy Grilled Cheese Sandwich Grilled cheese with onions, tomatoes and jalapenos&amp;ndash; tastier than the original!
Prep: 2 mins
Cook: 3 mins
Total: 5 mins
Servings: 2
Yield: 2 sandwiches
Ingredients 2 tablespoons butter or margarine 4 slices white bread 2 slices American cheese 1 roma (plum) tomato, thinly sliced ¼ small onion, chopped 1 jalapeno pepper, chopped Directions Step 1 Heat a large skillet over low heat. Spread butter or margarine onto one side of two slices of bread.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
