<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dinner on The Om Nommy</title>
    <link>/dinner/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dinner on The Om Nommy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/dinner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chicken and Waffles</title>
      <link>/dinner/dinner1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dinner/dinner1/</guid>
      <description>Chicken and Waffles This recipe has crunch, sweet and spicy, savory all in one.
Prep: 15 mins
Cook: 30 mins
Additional: 20 mins
Total: 1 hr 5 mins
Servings: 4
Yield: 4 sandwiches
Ingredients 4 eggs ¼ cup heavy cream 2 tablespoons cayenne pepper 1 tablespoon salt 1 tablespoon ground black pepper 2 cups all-purpose flour 1 cup cornstarch 1 tablespoon salt 1 quart peanut oil for frying 8 chicken tenders 1 cup mayonnaise ¼ cup maple syrup 2 teaspoons prepared horseradish 1 teaspoon dry mustard powder 12 slices bacon 8 thin slices Cheddar cheese 8 plain frozen waffles Directions **Step 1 Whisk together the eggs, cream, cayenne pepper, 1 tablespoon salt, and black pepper in a large bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Caesar Salad on a Stick</title>
      <link>/dinner/dinner2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dinner/dinner2/</guid>
      <description>Chicken Caesar Salad on a Stick This chicken Caesar-on-a-stick appetizer is a fun twist on a classic salad!
Prep: 10 mins
Total: 10 mins
Servings: 8
Yield: 8 servings
Ingredients 8 croutons 8 (1-inch) wedges romaine lettuce 8 (1 ounce) cubes cooked chicken 8 (1/2-inch) cubes Parmesan cheese, or to taste 8 bamboo toothpicks 8 teaspoons Caesar salad dressing Directions Step 1 Thread a crouton, romaine lettuce wedge, chicken cube, and Parmesan cheese cube onto each toothpick, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fruit Dip</title>
      <link>/dinner/dinner3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dinner/dinner3/</guid>
      <description>Fruit Dip Great with fresh fruit!
Servings: 24
Yield: 3 cups
Ingredients 8 ounces cream cheese ½ cup marshmallow creme 2 cups frozen whipped topping, thawed ¼ cup unsweetened pineapple juice Directions Step 1 Blend together the cream cheese, marshmallow cream and thawed topping. Add enough pineapple juice to make it dipping consistency. Chill for 1 hour. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
