<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nom begood</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on nom begood</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Banh Mi</title>
      <link>/lunch/lunch3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lunch/lunch3/</guid>
      <description>Banh Mi This banh mi (Vietnamese sandwich) is made with chicken and full of pickled vegetables.
Prep: 30 mins
Cook: 20 mins
Total: 50 mins
Servings:2 2
Yield: 1 12-inch sandwich
Ingredients ½ cup rice vinegar ¼ cup white sugar ¼ cup water ¼ cup matchstick-cut carrots ¼ cup peeled and matchstick-cut daikon radish ¼ cup thinly sliced white onion 1 skinless, boneless chicken breast half 1 pinch garlic salt, or to taste ground black pepper to taste 1 (12 inch) French baguette 4 tablespoons mayonnaise ¼ cup thinly sliced cucumber 1 tablespoon fresh cilantro leaves 1 small jalapeno pepper, cut into 1/16-inch-thick matchsticks 1 wedge lime Directions Step 1 Combine rice vinegar, sugar, and water in a saucepan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast: Perfect Summer Fruit Salad</title>
      <link>/breakfast/breakfast2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/breakfast/breakfast2/</guid>
      <description>Perfect Summer Fruit Salad The perfect fruit salad for a backyard bbq or any occasion.
Prep: 25 mins
Cook: 5 mins
Additional: 3 hrs
Total: 3 hrs 30 mins
Serving: 10
Yield: 10 servings
Ingredients ⅔ cup fresh orange juice ⅓ cup fresh lemon juice ⅓ cup packed brown sugar ½ teaspoon grated orange zest ½ teaspoon grated lemon zest 1 teaspoon vanilla extract 2 cups cubed fresh pineapple 2 cups strawberries, hulled and sliced 3 kiwi fruit, peeled and sliced 3 bananas, sliced 2 oranges, peeled and sectioned 1 cup seedless grapes 2 cups blueberries Directions Step 1 Bring orange juice, lemon juice, brown sugar, orange zest, and lemon zest to a boil in a saucepan over medium-high heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken and Waffles</title>
      <link>/dinner/dinner1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dinner/dinner1/</guid>
      <description>Chicken and Waffles This recipe has crunch, sweet and spicy, savory all in one.
Prep: 15 mins
Cook: 30 mins
Additional: 20 mins
Total: 1 hr 5 mins
Servings: 4
Yield: 4 sandwiches
Ingredients 4 eggs ¼ cup heavy cream 2 tablespoons cayenne pepper 1 tablespoon salt 1 tablespoon ground black pepper 2 cups all-purpose flour 1 cup cornstarch 1 tablespoon salt 1 quart peanut oil for frying 8 chicken tenders 1 cup mayonnaise ¼ cup maple syrup 2 teaspoons prepared horseradish 1 teaspoon dry mustard powder 12 slices bacon 8 thin slices Cheddar cheese 8 plain frozen waffles Directions **Step 1 Whisk together the eggs, cream, cayenne pepper, 1 tablespoon salt, and black pepper in a large bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Caesar Salad on a Stick</title>
      <link>/dinner/dinner2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dinner/dinner2/</guid>
      <description>Chicken Caesar Salad on a Stick This chicken Caesar-on-a-stick appetizer is a fun twist on a classic salad!
Prep: 10 mins
Total: 10 mins
Servings: 8
Yield: 8 servings
Ingredients 8 croutons 8 (1-inch) wedges romaine lettuce 8 (1 ounce) cubes cooked chicken 8 (1/2-inch) cubes Parmesan cheese, or to taste 8 bamboo toothpicks 8 teaspoons Caesar salad dressing Directions Step 1 Thread a crouton, romaine lettuce wedge, chicken cube, and Parmesan cheese cube onto each toothpick, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>first meal</title>
      <link>/breakfast/breakfast3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/breakfast/breakfast3/</guid>
      <description>Joy&amp;rsquo;s Easy Banana Bread This easy banana bread recipe is quick to prepare, and everyone always comes back for seconds!
Prep: 15 mins
Cook: 1 hr
Total: 1 hr 15 mins
Servings: 10
Yield: 1 9x5-inch loaf
Ingredients 3 ripe bananas, mashed 1 cup white sugar 1 egg ¼ cup melted butter 1 ½ cups all-purpose flour 1 teaspoon baking soda 1 teaspoon salt Directions Step 1 Preheat oven to 325 degrees F (165 degrees C).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fruit Dip</title>
      <link>/dinner/dinner3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dinner/dinner3/</guid>
      <description>Fruit Dip Great with fresh fruit!
Servings: 24
Yield: 3 cups
Ingredients 8 ounces cream cheese ½ cup marshmallow creme 2 cups frozen whipped topping, thawed ¼ cup unsweetened pineapple juice Directions Step 1 Blend together the cream cheese, marshmallow cream and thawed topping. Add enough pineapple juice to make it dipping consistency. Chill for 1 hour. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grilled Chicken Salad Sandwich</title>
      <link>/lunch/lunch2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lunch/lunch2/</guid>
      <description>Grilled Chicken Salad Sandwich This is a great way to use leftover grilled chicken breasts from dinner the night before.
Prep: 15 mins
Total: 15 mins
Servings: 4
Yield: 4 sandwiches
Ingredients 1 cup mayonnaise ⅛ teaspoon ground black pepper ⅛ teaspoon garlic powder ⅛ teaspoon celery salt 4 cups chopped leftover grilled chicken 2 celery stalks, sliced ½ cup sweetened dried cranberries ⅔ cup salted cashews 8 slices bread, toasted 4 tablespoons mayonnaise 4 large red leaf lettuce leaves 1 ripe tomato, sliced Directions Step 1 Whisk together 1 cup of mayonnaise, pepper, garlic powder, and celery salt until combined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lunch: Spicy Grilled Cheese Sandwich</title>
      <link>/lunch/lunch1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lunch/lunch1/</guid>
      <description>Spicy Grilled Cheese Sandwich Grilled cheese with onions, tomatoes and jalapenos&amp;ndash; tastier than the original!
Prep: 2 mins
Cook: 3 mins
Total: 5 mins
Servings: 2
Yield: 2 sandwiches
Ingredients 2 tablespoons butter or margarine 4 slices white bread 2 slices American cheese 1 roma (plum) tomato, thinly sliced ¼ small onion, chopped 1 jalapeno pepper, chopped Directions Step 1 Heat a large skillet over low heat. Spread butter or margarine onto one side of two slices of bread.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
